job-maldives.com 2011-05-19

# Job Maldives: Job Maldives Privacy Policy

**

**.**

 _"Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it."_ ****

**

 ** _._**

###  [Job Maldives Privacy Policy](http://www.job-maldives.com/2008/10/job-maldives-privacy-policy.html)

**Job Maldives Privacy Policy**

Job Maldives has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our respect for the privacy of our members and visitors to Job Maldives. Job Maldives will provide a link to this privacy policy on all pages that ask for your personal information.

The following privacy policy explains our practices for gathering and using information from our members and visitors to Job Maldives.

 **Cookies and IP Addresses**  
Job Maldives tracks IP addresses to measure traffic on our sites. Our web server automatically recognizes domain names and e-mail addresses for each visitor to our web sites. We do not use IP addresses to determine any user's identity. Students, graduates, job seekers, employer/recruiters, career services professionals, faculty, administration, and others who use our web sites are not required to accept cookies.

A cookie is a piece of data that Job Maldives stores on your computer when you visit our web sites. Some cookies coordinate advertising seen on the Job Maldives web sites. Cookies also track the pages that you have visited. The only personal information that a cookie contains is information you supply. A cookie cannot read other data from your computer's hard disk.

 **Outside Web Sites and Banner Advertisers**  
Job Maldives contains links to other sites. Job Maldives is not responsible for the privacy practices of such web sites. Inclusion of links to an outside web site, whether in an advertisement or content area of Job Maldives, is not an endorsement of the outside web site or a guarantee that the information it contains is accurate.

Job Maldives web site, also contains advertising from vendors of products and services that may be of interest to you. Job Maldives has no way of knowing whether those advertisers use cookies with their advertising and cannot guarantee that if you click on a banner, you will not be required to accept a cookie from the advertiser. You should contact the advertiser to determine its polices regarding use of cookies.

Job postings that are indexed on the Job Maldives are contributions from Direct Employers. 

**Forms  
** You may be asked to use an online form to register for the free Job Maldives newsletter, to send a Job Advertisement, to distribute a CV, win a prize, or register an opinion. 

These forms typically ask for:  
-contact information (such as your name or e-mail address),  
-demographic information (for example, your age, location, type of organization).

Contact information from these forms is used only for the purposes noted with the form such as delivery of the newsletter to your e-mail box.  

Information from these forms is also used by Job Maldives to send you information about products, services, news updates, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of this by clicking in the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of all Job Maldives newsletters

 **Mailing Labels/E-mail Addresses**  
Job Maldives does not sell or provide any of the e-mail addresses, phone numbers, or other personally identifiable information that it collects on its web sites to any individual or organization for commercial purposes. Job Maldives uses the information collected to improve the content of our web sites; to enhance existing products, services, and member benefits; and to plan for new products, services, and member benefits. Job Maldives may also collect aggregate information about which pages visitors access as they use the Job Maldives web sites. In addition, contact information may be provided to a third party to facilitate delivery of Job Maldives related materials, e.g., electronic newsletters; in such circumstances, the third party agrees not to sell or use the information except for the purposes Job Maldives contracted.  

 **Security  
** This web site takes every precaution to protect user information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, the information is protected both online and off-line.  
All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  
This site uses firewalls to protect from loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Getting Off the Mailing List**  
If you no longer wish to receive communications from Job Maldives or no longer want to subscribe to the Job Maldives daily Job Alerts, you may specify what you want to "opt out" of by sending a note to the following:

 **Changes to Privacy Policy  
** Job Maldives reserves the right to alter its privacy policies. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. For members of Job Maldives, this privacy statement is a supplement to, not a replacement for, any other agreements or terms already provided by Job Maldives to you.

 **Contacting the Web Site  
** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, please contact the following:  
Webmaster  
Job Maldives Team (JMT)  

“We have used several job sites in the past, both free and prepaid. Whilst several of the sites have been fairly good and met with the majority of our requirements, we have recently started to use “Job Maldives” and we are extremely impressed. The site is extremely logical and easy to use. _

_

We have had an excellent response from a diversified pool of potential candidates for our group, all of whom are of a very high quality and meet very well with the requirements of the roles advertised. We have had a far superior and better service from "Job Maldives" on free than we have had from some sites to whom we have paid a monthly service fee. We would highly recommend "Job Maldives" site to all candidates or clients, and we believe that this is the best place to be for any Employer or Employee in Maldives. THANK YOU JOB MALDIVES TEAM FOR YOUR VALUED SERVICE TO MALDIVES EMPLOYMENT INDUSTRY”.

_

_

Assistant Manager, Administration

 _____________________________________________________________________

 _"Thank you Job Maldives Team. We have found this website very effective and useful in reaching to a diverse pool of potential candidates for our Company. We were able to receive numerous amounts of resumes from all over Asia within a short period of time. The services which you provide are exceptional. We will be sure to post our future vacancies in the Job Maldives webpage. Thank you"._

Azfa

Human Resources Department

Rainbow Group of Companies

___________________________________________________________________

 _"I take the opportunity to note that, till date I have not had any better response from any other media of advertising as compared to the response I have had from my advertisements on Job-Maldives. I believe this is the best place to be for any Employer or Employee in Maldives"._

Moobeen Jaleel 

Branch Manager

MICROS-Fidelio Singapore Pte Ltd

___________________________________________________________________

 _"Job-Maldives.com is the best Job site I have ever found. Its really easy to contact the employer with your site. Thanks a lot"._ =ashis=

___________________________________________________________________

 _"I have got my dream job recently from one of the best resorts in Maldives and I found it from Job-Maldives. thank you very much"_.=Antony=  

___________________________________________________________________

 _"Your site is totally different from other jobsites but it is much better than other jobsites becaues i am always able to contact the employer without posting my resume on the website. Really appreciate it"_. =anil=  
___________________________________________________________________
